http://www.ktbs.com/site/privacy.html

Shreveport, LA
(71104)
Today
Showers and scattered thunderstorms. Storms may contain strong gusty winds. High 66F. Winds S at 10 to 15 mph. Chance of rain 100%..
Tonight
Thunderstorms in the evening will give way to partly cloudy skies overnight. Storms may contain strong gusty winds. Low 48F. Winds W at 5 to 10 mph. Chance of rain 90%.
Updated: December 11, 2020 @ 12:36 am
Full Forecast
Facebook
Twitter
Pinterest
Instagram
News
Weather
Sports
Community
Video
Watch Live
What's On TV
June 4, 2007What this Privacy Policy CoversThis Privacy Policy covers:KTBS.com and KTBS, Inc.'s treatment of personally identifiable information that KTBS.com collects when you are on the KTBS.com site, and when you use KTBS.com's services. This policy also covers KTBS.com's treatment of any personally identifiable information that KTBS.com's business partners share with KTBS.com or that KTBS.com may collect on a partner's site. This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that KTBS.com and KTBS, Inc. does not own or control, or to people that KTBS.com and KTBS, Inc. does not employ or manage.Information Collection and UseKTBS.com and KTBS, Inc. collects personally identifiable information when you register for a KTBS.com account, when you use certain KTBS.com products or services, when you visit KTBS.com pages, and when you enter promotions or sweepstakes. KTBS.com may also receive personally identifying information from our business partners. Prior to providing KTBS.com with information, you will be offered a link that allows you to review this privacy policy and you will be provided with an opportunity to opt-out of certain uses of your personal information when applicable.When you register with KTBS.com, we ask for your name, email address, physical address, zip code, phone and fax numbers, and comments. If you are commenting on a story, you will be required to provide your Facebook username and password if you are not already logged as a Facebook user. Once you register with KTBS.com and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us.KTBS.com uses information for two general purposes: to fulfill your requests for certain products and services, and to contact you about new products.We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click herehttp://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp.Information Sharing and DisclosureKTBS.com and KTBS, Inc. will not sell or rent your personally identifiable information to anyone.KTBS.com and KTBS, Inc. may send personally identifiable information about you to other companies or people when:We have your consent to share the information; We need to share your information to provide the product or service you have requested; We require opt-in consent to share your personally identifiable information.We respond to subpoenas, court orders or legal process; or We find that your actions on our website violate the KTBS.com Terms of Service or any of our usage guidelines for specific products or servicesCookiesWhen you visit KTBS.com, we send one or more cookies to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser. We use cookies to improve the quality of our service by storing user preferences and tracking user trends. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies, but you can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some KTBS.com features and services may not function properly if your cookies are disabled.Other companies' use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not this one. Advertisers or other companies do not have access to KTBS.com's cookies.To request changes to or deletion of your KTBS.com account, and to read about what information may possibly remain in our archived records after your account has been deleted email us at bpollitt@ktbs.com.SecurityThis site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control.Changes to this Privacy PolicyKTBS.com and KTBS, Inc. may amend this policy from time to time. If we make any substantial changes in the way we use your personal information we will notify you by posting a prominent announcement on our pages.
View Full Screen
Stocks
Market Data by TradingView
Online Poll
During this pandemic, are you doing more holiday shopping online?
You voted:
© Copyright 2020 KTBS 3, 312 E. Kings Hwy Shreveport, LA | Terms of Use | Privacy Policy
Powered by BLOX Content Management System from TownNews.com.
